<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
 <title>LibreNMS Notifications</title>
 <description>RSS feed for notifications to LibreNMS users</description>
 <link>http://www.librenms.org/</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 <ttl>1800</ttl>
 
 <item>
  <title>Hello World!</title>
  <description>This is the first notification. We will post these whenever an upcoming major change is about to happen.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Important update being released</title>
  <description>We are releasing an important update within the next 24 hours which provides some additional functionality when running daily.sh. Whilst we have done everything we can to test this across as many platforms as possible we thought it was worth letting you know.\n\nIf you notice issues with further updates after this one then please get in touch with us on either IRC or GitHub.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Poller changes</title>
  <description>Earlier this month we released some updates which enable alpha versions of InfluxDB and MIB-based polling.\nWe have some further updates planned for the near future which may affect polling, so if you are running a mission-critical LibreNMS instance, you may wish to consider disabling updates for the time being.\nIf you notice any issues, please get in touch with us via IRC or GitHub.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Imagemagick vulnerability</title>
  <description>A vulnerability in ImageMagick has been released, please see https://imagetragick.com/ for more details.\n\nLibreNMS uses ImageMagick for pdf generation, we advise that you add the temporary fix in on the aforementioned website until patches for your distribution are available to update ImageMagick.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Component Alerting Change</title>
  <description>On July 25th we will be merging a PR that changes the status codes that are used for the component feature. If you have alerting rules that reference component.status, %macros.component_alert or %macros.component_normal please disable these until after the PR has been merged. Updated documentation will be merged with the PR to: http://docs.librenms.org/Extensions/Component/#alert</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 25 July 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>NUT Ups Application monitoring update</title>
  <description>On December 20th we will be merging a PR that fixes the polling of data for NUT Ups devices.\n\nUnfortunately this will require users to delete the existing data and allow it to be re-created.\n\nTo do this, you can delete rrd files app-ups-nut-ID.rrd. ID will be a unique ID. After removing this file then data collection will start again.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 18 December 2016 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Multimatic UPS detection changes</title>
  <description>On December 21st we will be merging a PR that will change devices currently detected as multimatic to be detected as generex-ups.\n\nIf you have any alert rules or device groups that rely on this OS definition then you will need to update those rules to include generex-ups.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 18 December 2016 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Redback SmartEdge OS change</title>
  <description>On January 19th we will be merging a PR that will change devices currently detected as redback to be detected as seos.\n\nIf you have any alert rules or device groups that rely on this OS definition then you will need to update those rules to include seos.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 15 January 2016 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Large schema update due to be released</title>
  <description>Please see: https://community.librenms.org/t/large-schema-update-being-released/637 for further info.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 22 February 2017 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Change to extremeware and xos discovery</title>
  <description>On the 10th of March, we are changing the way that OS detection is done for Extremeware and XOS devices, this could lead to the OS changing so if you have alerting or groups that reference these os names then please be aware that you will need to update them.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 6 March 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Change to Ubiquiti Airfibre device type</title>
  <description>On the 24th of March, we are changing device type for Ubiquiti AirFibre from network to wireless. See https://github.com/librenms/librenms/pull/6160 for PR.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 20 March 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Change to some DNOS discovery</title>
  <description>On the 24th of March, we are changing the detection of some Dell DNOS devices to PowerConnect. This is to show the difference between v6 and v9 of the DNOS OS. See https://github.com/librenms/librenms/pull/6206 for PR.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 March 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Change to Cisco UCM type from tele to collaboration</title>
  <description>On the 10th of April 2017, we are changing the type Cisco UCM (cucm) devices from tele to collaboration. If you have any alert rules or groups based on this value please adjust them after the daily update on that date.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 6 April 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
  <item>
  <title>Change to AXIS OS device type</title>
  <description>On the 17th of April 2017, we are changing the device type of AXIS devices from network to appliance. If you have any alert rules or groups based on this value please adjust them after the daily update on that date.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 13 April 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
  <item>
  <title>Change to MGE, Eaton, and Powerware UPS os</title>
  <description>On the 24th of April 2017, The following UPS devices os will change: mgeups(Galaxy)->apc-mgeups, mgeups->eaton-mgeups, powerware->eatonups.  If you have any alert rules or groups based on this value please adjust them after the daily update on that date.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 April 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Change to IRC alerts</title>
  <description>On the 8th of June 2017, we will change the way the ircbot displays alerts.  It will now start using the standard templating system.  You can customize the alert templates for irc using e.g. {if %transport == irc}.  Please be aware that overly long templates might lead to the bot being disconnected for excess flood.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 1 June 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Change Cisco Unified CM (cucm) detection to be ucos (Cisco Unified Communication OS)</title>
  <description>On the 17th of June 2017, we are changing the os name of cucm to ucos to be inline with the Cisco name.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 13 June 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Change Ubiquiti AirOS (airos) device type </title>
  <description>On the 10th of July 2017, we are changing the device type of Ubiquiti AirOS devices from network to wireless. If you have any alert rules or groups based on this value please adjust them after the daily update on that date.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 3 July 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>PowerWalker devices will now use the EPPC MIB for sensors</title>
  <description>On the 20th of July 2017, we are changing the PowerWalker OS to use the EPPC MIB for sensor data. This will bring with it some additional metrics but will also mean that historical graphs will no longer be available. If you require this data then we suggest you copy the rrd files out of the way for later use.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 13 July 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>EricssonLG iPECS devices OS name change</title>
  <description>On the 25th of September 2017, we are changing the OS names for the ELG iPECS UCP from ipecs -> elg-ipecs-ucp and for the ELG iPECS ES from ericsson-es -> elg-ipecs-es. Please adjust any alert rules or device groups that use these OS names.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Cisco SMB Linux OS changing to Cisco WAP</title>
  <description>On the 27th of October 2017, we are changing the OS names for the Cisco SMB Linux devices from ciscosmblinux -> ciscowap. Please adjust any alert rules or device groups that use these OS names.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>API update will enforce user permissions, check your tokens</title>
  <description>Please see https://community.librenms.org/t/api-update-will-enforce-user-permissions-check-your-api-tokens/2675 for more info</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Cambium Refactor</title>
  <description>On the 6th of December 2017, we are changing the OS names for all cambium products to their respective category. (Ex: pmp, ptp650, ptp250, cmm) Please adjust any alert rules or device groups that use these OS names. This will bring with it some additional metrics but will also mean that some historical graphs will no longer be available. </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
</channel>
</rss>
